

GEOMATIC ENGINEERING & GIS | WEB DEVELOPMENT

I am a geospatial specialist with a minimum of two years in the field. Professionally, I am determined, self-motivated hardworking to ensure that I maximize on the knowledge I have. In relation to technology, I am working smart to be updated with location intelligence and artificial intelligence in general. I do have team work, leadership skills that form part of my professional well being.

+254 7 463 426 79 alfredamboxan.wegner@gmail.com P.O BOX 62000, 00100, NAIROBI, KENYA

English --- - Fluent. Swahili --- - Proficient Luhya --- - Fluent

- Reading (tech articles & books)
- Playing football
- Nature walk
- Travel explore new areas.

Provided on request.

Work Experience

01/2022 - 04/2022 • Attachee | GIS Specialist.

Vihiga County | Address: P.O BOX 344-50300, Maragoli.

- Perform spatial analysis and visualization of data.
- Digitization of analogue maps.
- Spatial collection using available tools and technologies.
- Update collected data into database system.
- Programming and automating tasks
- Spatial data processing, and adding spatial attribute to data.e.t.c

04/2021 - 06/2021 Freelancer GIS Specialist.

Upwork; Online.

- Spatial data processing, analysis and visualization.
- Digitization of maps using skyline explorer (3D scene)
- Research for topic specifed by client majoring in GIS context.
- Perform deep learng and develop prediction model.

05/2018 - 08/2018

Volunteer Peer Teacher.

Ekwanda High Sch. | Address: P.O BOX 285- 40105, Maseno.

- -Teaching mathematics, physics, and chemistry.
- In charge of math hour for the whole school.
- Coach students in practical field works and lead Innovation club.

Education Background.

08/2018 - Present •Bsc. Geomatic Engineering and GIS.

Jomo Kenyatta University of Agriculture and Technology (JKUAT) Address: P.O BOX 62000-00100, Nairobi. Course duration - 5 years. Grade / GPA ----- N/A

02/2014 - 12/2017 ♦ Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education(KCSE).

Ekwanda High School

Address: P.O BOX 285-40105, Maseno. Study duration - 4 years. Grade / GPA ----- B+ | GPA -- 3.78

01/2005 - 11/2013 ♦ Kenya Certificate of Primary Education(KCPE).

Esibembe Primary School.

Address: P.O BOX 21-40105, Maseno. Study duration - 8 years. Grade / GPA ----- B | GPA -- 3.55

Key Skills.

- Geospatial information systems(GIS)
- Remote Sensing
- photogrammetry

- Engineering survey

- Database

- Machine learning (Python)
- Frontend web development.
- Advance research
- Project management
- Cadastral surveying.
- CAD/CAM/Engineering design. Statistical Analysis and Data analytics.
 - Data collection and engineering.
- Communication skills.

Awards and Achievments.

- Website challenge winner awarded by JKUAT club through the the department chairperson.
- Best student leader of the year awarded at Ekwanda High school for being examplary academic student leader to be emulated.